Guide to the National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter (NOW-NYC) Records TAM.106
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Committees
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee--NOW-N.Y. State Lobby Day, Albany, N.Y., March 23, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Legislative and Political Affairs Committee--WomanPower, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lesbian Rights Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Marriage and Family Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee--Equal Rights Divorce Reform Bill, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee--State Conference on Marriage and Divorce, January 19-20, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee--Task Force on Battered Wives, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Marriage and Divorce Committee, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Family Relations Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Membership Committee, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Membership Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee--Men's Action Group, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Membership Committee--Requests for Information, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Membership Committee, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Membership Committee--Renewals, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Membership Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Membership Committee--Renewals and Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Membership Committee, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Membership List, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Membership Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Membership Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Minority Women's Issues Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Over-45 Committee, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Over-45 Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Older Women's Issues Committee, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Older Women's Issues Committee, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Program Committee, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Psychology Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Psychology Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Psychology Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations Committee--Clippings (Apr-Jun 1974) (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Library (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Library (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Membership, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Petitions, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Rape Victims, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rape Prevention Committee (1/74-6/74), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention Committee (7/74-12/74), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Binder Materials, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Focus 15, circa 1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Grant Applications, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Mayor's Task Force on Rape, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Minutes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Newsletter, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Questionnaires, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Rape Speakers Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Rape Prevention Committee-- "Rape, the Law, and You" Broadcast Transcript, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention Committee-- "Rape, the Law, and You" Notes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--United Nations Force in Cypress--Report of Turkish Atrocities, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rape Prevention Committee (1/75-6/75), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rape Prevention Committee (7/75-12/75), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Joan Little Case, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Martin Evans Rape Trial, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Mayor's Task Force on Rape, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Minutes, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Research--Self Defense, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Minutes, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Rape Prevention Committee--Women's Walk Against Rape, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Sex Education, Contraception, and Abortion Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Sexism in Religion Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Sexuality Committee--Feminist Sexuality Project, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sexuality Committee--Women's Sexuality Conference, June 9-10, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sexuality Committee--Women's Sexuality Conference, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sexuality and Lesbianism Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Sexuality and Interpersonal Relations Committee, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Textbook Committee, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Writers Committee, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Series V: Programs, 1969-1984
  This series covers events and projects by NOW--New York Chapter that do not fall under the jurisdiction of a committee. These events range from the broad, multi-issue "Women Strike for Equality" in 1971 to the narrower-focused "Endowed Chair" project (1973-76) through which NOW named its conference room chairs after renowned women in history. This series is arranged alphabetically by program.
  - Assertiveness Training Workshop, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - August 26th Packet, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - AWARE day fair, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Cable Television Series, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Women's Liberation, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Conferences and Conventions, 2012-2016 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Endowed Chair Project, 1973, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Equality in Mortgage Lending--articles, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Feminist Community Press Conference, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - First Day Covers, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Herstory Project, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - International Women's Year (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - International Women's Day, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Training Workshop--December 13, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Mother's Day Bill of Rights, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - National NOW Conference Denver, CO "Toxic Tax Syndrome", 1986 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Our North American Foremothers slide show--option agreements, correspondence., 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Our North American Foremothers slide show--script, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Public Speaking Workshop, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Speakers, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1984, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1994-2010 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Tenth Anniversary Gala Banquet--March 25, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Town Hall Celebration of the Arts, January 10-February 14, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Town Hall "Dialogue on Women's Liberation", 1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Urban Woman's Conference, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Womanpower Project, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Women: A Political Force Conference, November 13-14, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Women and AIDS: Exploring the Issues, Jan 28, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Women of Power and Influence Awards, 1995-2019 (Box 105, Folder 4-7)
  - Women of Vision Awards, 1982-2001 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Women Strike for Equality, August 26, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Women March for Equality, August 26, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Women March for Justice and Equality, August 26, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Women's Film Program, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Women's Health Conference, NYC, Nov. 18-21, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Women's History Series, 1980-1981 (Box 106, Folder 1-6)
  - Youth/NOW, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Series VI: National and Regional NOW, 1966-1993
  These files are arranged chronologically within each of the following subheadings: National NOW, Regional NOWs, NOW--New York State, Local Chapters of NOW. Materials include agendas, brochures, clippings, conference schedules, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, position statements, reports, resolutions.
  1. National NOW. Materials on the national conferences make up the bulk of these files. Other notable information includes 1973-president Wilma Scott Heide's correspondence from 1970 to 1971, 1973 election forms for candidates to National Board of Directors, material from the General Mills boycott in 1973, and material from the dissident group Majority Caucus that arose within NOW in 1975.
  2. Regional NOWs (East, West, etc.). The major event in these files is the 1972 Eastern Regional Conference, held in Pittsburgh.
  3. NOW--New York State. State conferences such as "Women: A Political Force" appear in these folders' materials, including forms, mailing addresses, memoranda, programs for conferences.
  4. Local chapters of NOW. These folders contain materials from local NOW chapters throughout the United States. Materials include flyers, announcements, newsletters, and programs. This section is arranged chronologically.
  5. Related arms of NOW-N.Y.C.: A. The Service Fund of NOW-N.Y.C.; B. NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund; C. WomanPower PAC
  - National NOW, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National NOW, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National NOW, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National NOW, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National NOW, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National NOW (Jan-June 1973) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National NOW (Jul-Dec 1973) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National NOW--Conference, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National NOW--Origins and History, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National Task Force--Rape Prevention, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National NOW, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - National NOW, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - National NOW, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National NOW, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National NOW, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National NOW, 1979, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Central Region, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Region, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Region, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Region, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Northeast Region, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Western Region, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - NOW New York State, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - NOW New York State, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - NOW New York State, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - NOW New York State, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - NOW New York State, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - NOW New York State, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - NOW New York State, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - NOW New York State, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NOW New York State, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NOW New York State, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Local Chapters, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Local Chapters, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Local Chapters, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Local Chapters, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Local Chapters, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Local Chapters, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Local Chapters, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Local Chapters, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Local Chapters, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Local Chapters, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Service Fund of NOW-N.Y.C., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Service Fund of NOW-N.Y.C., 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Service Fund of NOW-N.Y.C., 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund--Blumberg Law Suit (Maternity Leave), 1971 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - NOW Legal Defense & Education Fund--Paternity Leave Lawsuit, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund--Equal Rights for Women Campaign, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - WomanPower PAC, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Series VII: NOW and Other Groups, 1969-1982
  This series includes materials from other feminist groups that were NOW's contemporaries in the women's movement. NOW often worked through coalitions, as in the ones organized to sponsor the large demonstrations for reproductive rights. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject; thus, coalitions are located under their subject area (e.g., REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS--WOMEN'S ABORTION ACTION COALITION"). Multi-issue feminist groups like NOW are found under the heading FEMINIST GROUPS.
  - Arts--Women's Interart Center, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Arts--other groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Child Care--other groups, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Education--other groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Employment--other groups, 1970-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - E.R.A.--other groups, 1970-1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Feminist Groups--Congress to Unite Women, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Feminist Groups--Feminist Forums, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Groups--National Black Feminist Organization, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Feminist Groups--New York City Feminist Community Coalition, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Feminist Groups--New York Radical Feminists, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Feminist Groups--other, 1971-1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Health--other groups, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Herstory--other groups, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Image of Women--other groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Image of Women--Women in Media Alliance, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - International Women's Movement, 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Legislation and Politics--National Women's Political Caucus, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Legislation and Politics--National Women's Political Caucus, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Legislation and Politics--other groups, 1967-1976 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Lesbian Rights--other groups, 1970-1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Marriage and Divorce--other groups, 1971-1977 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Newspapers--other, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Older Women's Issues--other groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Prostitution--other groups, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Rape Prevention--Inez Garcia Defense Committee, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Rape Prevention--New York Rape Coalition, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Rape Prevention--New York Women Against Rape, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Rape Prevention--Women Organized Against Rape, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Rape Prevention--Women's Anti-Rape Coalition, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Rape Prevention--other groups, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Reproductive Rights--other groups, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Reproductive Rights--Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Reproductive Rights--Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Reproductive Rights--Women's National Abortion Action Coalition (WONAAC), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Reproductive Rights--Women's National Abortion Coalition, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Sports--other groups, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- Series VIII: Photographs and Negatives
  Series consists of black and white and color photographs, negatives, contact sheets, and slides from NOW-NYC events, rallies, and meetings, portraits of staff and the Board of Directors, and publicity photographs. Includes campaigns and rallies of the Reproductive Rights, Reproduction and its Control, E.R.A., and Rape Prevention Committees, marches on behalf of local and national electoral campaigns, and NOW-NYC member participation in National NOW conferences. Materials date from circa 1960s-1980s.
  - 24 hour Watch for the E.R.A., Aug 26, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - A.A.A. Pregnancy Problem Clinic [Contact Sheet, Print and Negatives], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Abortion March New York Foley Square, Jul 5, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Abortion March-Washington Press Conference, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - Abortion-Operation Rescue, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  - Abortion Protest-Bush, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Abortion Protest Saint Patrick's, Feb 1989 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - "April March Against the War" [Photograph by Judith Brown], [1970] (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Art, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Art -- Sojourner Truth and Esther Morris, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Arts Committee, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Images, circa 1970-1984 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Awards-Susan B. Anthony, 1980, 1985, 1988, 1989, undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - ["Awards-Susan B Anthony"- 1985 Negatives] (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - [Awards-Others], 1987, 1990, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Bella Abzug, 1981, undated (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors [Polaroid Portraits], 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Brian Palmer Photos - Operation Rescue, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Celebrate Suffrage Fundraiser, Summer 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Cherry Hill Demonstration, undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Committee Members and Others [Polaroid Portraits], Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Demonstration at fake abortion clinic "Options", Jul 30, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - [Demonstration at Fake Abortion Clinic "Options" -Negatives], Jul 30, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Demonstration- "Divorce: American Style" at Court Building, 1985? (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - [Demonstration-"Divorce: American Style"-Negatives"], 1985? (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Demonstration-Photos by Gina Salth, Jan 22, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - [Demonstration-Photos by Gina Salth-Negatives], Jan 22, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Election Eve Party at NOW-1984/Betty Friedan on NOW's "Birthday" October 1984 (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Elections-Officers, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Endorsement, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - E.R.A. Campaigns, Jun 1982, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - E.R.A. Committee: "NOW Goes to Virginia for the E.R.A." [Photograph by Jean Vertheim], Jan 21, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - E.R.A. Committee: E.R.A. March, Chicago, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - E.R.A. Vigil Women's Equality Day, Aug 22, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Fundraiser, Aug 26, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Fundraiser, July 17 and 28 [year unknown] (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Gay Pride, Mar 1989 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - [Gay Pride? -Washington D.C.], 1993 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - [Gay Pride? - Washington D.C.- Negatives], 1993 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - [Group Portraits], 1994, undated (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Insurance Demonstration, undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - ["Insurance Demonstration"-Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Jerry Skohle, Aug 22, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - ["Jerry Skohle" -Negatives], Aug 22, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Labor Day, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - "Let's Stop the Violence" [Photographs by Edye Falencki], 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lobbying-Albany, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mademoiselle Magazine Awards: Anne Grant, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - "March for Women's Equality/Women's Lives" [Contact Sheets and Prints], Apr 9, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - [Miscellaneous Conferences], undated (Box 43, Folder 58)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations/Rallies-Dated], late 1970s-early 1990s (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations/Rallies-Undated] (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations/Rallies-Undated] (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - [Miscellaneous Demonstrations/Rallies-Undated-Contacts with Negatives] (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - [Miscellaneous Events-Specified-Dated and undated], 1980-1991, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - [Miscellaneous Individuals], 1979, undated (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - [Miscellaneous Marches-Dated], 1978 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  - [Miscellaneous Marches-Undated] (Box 43, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - National and Regional NOW: National NOW Convention, San Antonio, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - National and Regional NOW: National NOW Convention, Miami, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - National NOW Conference, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - National NOW Conference-Denver, CO-March and Rally, Jun 1986 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  - ["National NOW Conference-Denver, CO-March and Rally" Negatives], Jun 1986 (Box 43, Folder 54)
  - National NOW Conference-Miami, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  - National NOW Conference Rally to Overturn the Gag Rule, Jul 1991 (Box 43, Folder 55)
  - ["National NOW Conference Rally to overturn the Gag Rule"-Negatives], Jul 1991 (Box 43, Folder 56)
  - National NOW Conference-New Orleans, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  - ["National NOW Conference- New Orleans" -Negatives], 1985 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - National NOW Conference-Washington D.C., 1983 (Box 43, Folder 48)
  - Negatives -- Rallies and Meetings, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - NOW Direct Market Training Program, Feb 4, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - NOW NY State Conference Includes: Noreen Lonnell, Barbara Ehrenreich, Judy Goldsmith, Carol Bellamy, Janice LaPorche, Muriel Fox, Bella Abzug, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 52)
  - NOW/NYC Elections Includes: Jennifer Brown, Carolyn Chambers, Kelli Conlin, Ann Colona, Trish Bellae, Francois Jacobsohn, Karen Rood, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - ["NOW/NYC Elections 1988"-Negatives] (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - NOW/NYC Elections Includes: S. Hartnett, S.Spaulding, Jennifer Brown, V. Partridge, D. Welsh, N. Northup, M. Williams, L. Baldwin, S. Lombard, M. Giomonsis [?], 1985 (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - NOW State Conference, undated (Box 43, Folder 57)
  - Operation Rescue-Dobbs Ferry, Dec 1988 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  - Operation Rescue-Planned Parenthood, undated (Box 43, Folder 41-42)
  - ["Operation Rescue-Planned Parenthood"-Negatives], undated (Box 43, Folder 43)